Killing your dream? we'll have
the wedding when you get back.
Yeah, but what about all the plans
and the guests?
(Bernadette:)We'll call them.
AIthough my dad's gonna go
a little nutso over losing his deposits.
(Howard:)You're right, he is.
(Howard:)Your dad's gonna be furious.
(Howard:)There's no way he's gonna let us
postpone this wedding.
(Howard:)Well, we tried.
(Bernadette:)I'll talk to him.
He won't say no to his little girl, heh.
No, l... I should talk to him.
You know, man to man.
(Bernadette:)Howie, my dad can be a bully.
(Bernadette:)He's gonna make you cancel
your flight.
Yeah, we can only hope, heh,
that he doesn't.
(Sheldon:)Bishop to queen four, level two.
(Leonard:)- Check.
- Sheldon, Knight takes Bishop.
(Leonard:)You all right?
(Sheldon:)I'm fine.
(Leonard:)Are you? You left your queen exposed
from above...